Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of New York City Miscellaneous Manuscripts, circa 1614-1933 (bulk 1641-1900) MS 443.19
New-York Historical Society
- Petition of Owners of property adjoining Christopher Street to the Mayor regarding widening Christopher Street, 1811 August (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Depositions of Isaac Mead and Abraham Varick, 1811 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Certificate of Manumission, signed by Mayor Dewitt Clinton, 1812 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  Enslaved woman Isabel freed by Peter Wilson, professor of Languages, Columbia College
- A Copy of Letter from Richard Varick to the Chairman of the Federal Committee of New York City, 1812 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  Convention postponed but delegates still appointed
- Permission to Sell Liquor granted to Henry Gifford, 1812 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Final Settlement between US and John Newkirk, 1813 July 15 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  US owed John Newkirk $2.00. First final settlement certificate issued in State of New York
- Copy of Minutes of Council held at Fort George, 1813 September 20 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Earl of Loudoun saw papers from Mr. Livingston and ordered guard to be sent to Manor if Mr. Livingston applied for one.
- Deposition of Abraham Merritt, 1814 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- 2 Documents of John F. Randolph of New York City Administrator: Official document re mortgage; official document re lease, 1815 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Document giving Isaac Bell the vote of Mary Ellis in any vote for the Directors of the Bank of New York, 1815 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Inventory of Monies, Goods, Wares & Merchandises Remaining Unclaimed in the Police Department of New York City, 1815 January (Box 6, Folder 59)
- George Lorillard is entitled to two shares of Bank of New York, 1816 July 17 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Document of Horace Holden, 1816 November 13 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Constitution of New York Bibliographical Society, 1816 February (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Handwritten note states that Body of document in handwriting of Governor Clinton
- Group of 19 payment warrants for various services, labor and/or supplies to Corporation of New York, 1816, 1818, 1820, 1821, 1830, 1831, 1843 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Inspectors of State Prison Contracts concerning State Prison regarding providing prisoners with rations and provisions to hospital and hospital stores, 1817 April 15 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Petition of Butchers of the Collect Market to Mayor regarding placing market on Collect Street between Franklin and Anthony Streets, 1817 July 10 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Lt. Col. Nathaniel Weed appear and testify before Court Martial of Cornelius Oakley - City of New York, 1817 November 7 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Undersigned Endorsement of the appointment of Colonel Christian to the office of Police Justice of New York, 1818 March 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Appointment of George B. Smith to Collector of Arrears of Taxes, by Mayor, Aldermen & Commonalty of New York, 1819 July 21 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Deposition of Richard Ely and Search Warrant, 1820 January 20 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Stolen trunk with coats, pantaloons and vests. Warrant to search cellar of house on Gold Street and Eders Alley
- Received from City of New York $29,448.29 for loss in relinquishing the deserted land in the Second Ward, 1821 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Appointment of George B. Smith Assistant State Commissioner by Aldermen, Mayor & Common Council of New York, 1821 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Letter from Judge Advocate General's Office RE: Application of Militia Regulations to the City of New York, 1821 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Questions regarding number of parades, court martial trials held in NYC
- Assorted Documents Including An Act for Preventing Usury, 1822 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  5 documents: No. 15 Harman Street must pave alley (directed to Stephen Beekman, agent for M.B. Talmage); Gazette to Sylanus Miller is undeliverable from Post-Office; James Boyle put in 5,569 loads of earth for lot on corner of West and Warren Streets (Isaac Ludlum, city surveyor); John Sharp testified that tenants, William Collins and Joseph Derve, owe rent; Act preventing Usury
- Rules & Regulations for the Government of a Hospital Department of the State Prison, 1822 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- List of Booksellers, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Pencil note: "Partial List of Booksellers about 1824"
- Certificate by Isaac Ludlum, City Surveyor, that lot filled by James Boyle finished agreeably to 2,776 loads, 1823 January 21 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Lot between Murray and Warren streets
- Certificate by Isaac Ludlum, City Surveyor, that James Boyle put 475 loads of earth more than survey, 1823 November (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Lot on West Street
- Election of Valentine Nutter as Church Warden of St. Mary's Episcopal Church, 1823 December 19 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- W. Shepard's List of tenants between Warren and Murray Streets, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Report of the Road Committee, 1824 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Bayard asked to open 15th, 16th, 17th Streets at 7th Avenue
- Letter of license to William Shaw, a Band Box Maker, 1824 November 12 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Order for the Arrest of William Sparks, 1824 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Jacob Ackerman accuses William Spark of taking one horse, one coat and harness, one bag of oats
- Papers RE: Real Estate Transactions, 1826-1829 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Butchers Licenses, 1826-1830 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Alexander Anthony, John Scott, Caleb Concklin, Gilbert Griffin, John Banker, Isaac Vawn, Daniel Hyde, Jacob Jacakes, Joshua Hyde, Isaac Valentine, Robert Denyke, Caleb Angevine, licensees
- Brief History of the New York Asylum for Lying-In Women, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
- 2 Appointments by the Mayor, Aldermen, Commonalty of the City of New York, 1827 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  John Sherwood, Measurer of Lumber; George B. Smith, Assistant Street Commissioner of the City of New York
- Stage Coach Licenses, 1827-1854 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  James Flanagan, Abraham Brower, James Dickerson, Joseph Palmer, Gideon Sampson, G.W. Littell, Gardner A. Sage, George W. Edwards, H.N. Stebbins, W.S. Corwin, licensees
- Remonstrance Against Opening Cedar Street, 1828 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Folder includes several supporting document to the Remonstrance
- Account of Sale of Minthorne Estate, 1829 March 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  J.M. Martin reporting sale of property near Bowery
- Unofficial records of Real Estate Transactions in New York City (lower Manhattan), 1829-1835 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- List of Names of Individuals who bought the State Prison lots sold by J. Bleeker, 1829 April 20 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Document and drawings of 3 lots sold by J. Bleeker, 1829 August (Box 7, Folder 16)
  One lot was at corner of Gold Street and Maiden Lane, other lots were between Exchange and Wall Streets near New Street
- Letter from the Committee of The New York Law Institute, 1829 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Letter requests passage of law to appoint a vice-chancellor to reside in New York City; Court of Chancery busy; Appointment of officer other than Circuit judge or Chancellor
- Papers of Gideon Lee Relating to The Road Committee, 1829-1831 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Papers RE: Real Estate Transactions, 1830-1831 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Letter from Committee in charge of Establishing University in the City of New York to Hon. R. Walworth, Chancellor, 1830 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Discussion as to University; J.W. Matthews, James M. Wainwright, and J. Delafield were the committee
- Sale of Property belonging to Elbert Anderson Estate, 1831 January 5,6 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  J. Bleeker reporting sale, property near the Bowery
- 2 Financial Documents: Transfer of 20 shares in New Haven Verd Antique Marble Company by Joseph Shannon to Alix Kunshud; Obligation of Thomas E. Davis to Nicholas W. Stuyvesant, 1832, 1838 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- 3 Documents: Circular re Cholera epidemic has passed with signed note by Arthur Tappan to Merchants, Chamberlain & Caldwell of Cincinnati,; List of goods sold by James Montgomery; Letter of Joseph Moulton to Col. Ralph E. W. Earl regarding location of Customs House, 1832-1833 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- 3 Letters: Constituent Letter to U.S. Representative Edward Curtis – series of questions on Slavery & Slave-Trade and his representation of New York in Congress; Unsigned reponse to Letter to Honorable Edward Curtis; Personal letter to E.S. Strike from cousin, 1834-1838 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Asks if Curtis favors immediate abolition of Slavery and Slave-Trade in District of Columbia and opposes annexation of Texas, among other questions; cousin's letter mentions funeral procession in memory of General Lafayette in New York City, fires, and meeting called by 5 important New York Merchants to preach against Slavery
- 2 North River Insurance Company Policies, 1836 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  Policies cover properties at 646 Water Street and 648 Water Street, New York City
- Receipt for 92 Cart-Loads of Street Manure, 1836 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  Placed on Vessel, Harstsacher, Captain Parish
- New York Collector's Office Real Estate Assessments, 1836-1842 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Assessments for widening street, repaving, bridges; many for Chapel Street
- Public Meeting of the Merchants, Traders and Mechanics of the City of New York on the Resumption of Specie Payments, with Signatures, 1837 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Signed by well-known merchants, traders and mechanics, such as John Jacob Astor
- Enrollment of Men of Companies C-H of the 258th Regiment, 1837 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  Rolls lists names by Companies, boundaries of each Company
- Documents RE: Widening and Extending of Anthony Street, 1837-1838 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Includes several pages of newspaper clippings
- 2 Documents: Letter of Howes Godphrey Robinson to George Trufant; Payroll, American Theater on ther Bowery, November 23, 1839, 1834 April 30; 1839 November 23 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  Letter regards the decline in the price of flour
- Letter to Lewis Selye, Esq. of Rochester, NY, from the Globe Fire Insurance Company, 1840 May 6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Letter from the Democratic Whig Young Men, with signatures of the Corresponding Committee, to "a reliable friend in every town in the State", 1840 July 4 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  A set of questions to determine the correct estimate for the Harrison and Seward majority at the approaching election
- Notices of General Committee of Democratic Whig Young Men, 1840-1841 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Notices for Dr. Benjamin A. Drake of 35 Bowery, folder also includes a list of members of General Committee for 1841.
- Memorial of the Chamber of Commerce of New York to the US Senate and House of Representatives, 1841 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  The Memorial concerns Bankruptcy Law
- Lease from the Mayor, Aldermen, and Commonalty of the City of New York to Daniel S. Darling, 1842 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Lease for well and dump on 19th Street near Tenth Avenue
- Search for Taxes on two lots on 18th street and notice of chancery sale of this property, 1844 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Chancery sale by Anthony Bleecker & Co.
- Translation of a composition of a deaf-mute of the New York Institution For The Deaf and Dumb, 1844 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Translation of a composition of a deaf-mute of the New York Institution For The Deaf and Dumb
- Signed Letter to Fire Warden from Occupants at 73 Allen Street, 1844 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Letter stating that neighborhood is not secure with match factory next door in wooden house
- Certificate of Copyright of the Book – A Brief Description of New York … by Daniel Denton, 1845 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Two documents of the Mariners Family Industrial Society, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  First document explains the creation of the Society to benefit the families of seamen, the profits from the clothing story which were used to benefit the Society, and a plea to donate to the Society; Second document is a reprint of an Address given to the Society by Reverend John S.C. Abbott
- Memorandum of Title of Thomas Boyd to property in 16th Street, 1845 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Property is on 16th Street east of 8th Avenue
- ALS from W. Havemeyer, Mayor of New York, to Assistant Justice Kirtland, 1845 August 5 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Act of Establishment and regulation of Police Force in force for several days – office of Marshals is abolished
- New York Scientific Association, 1845 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Includes Constitution, Duties of Officers and Minutes of meetings
- Petition to US Congress to form Congress of Nations to form a code of International Law, 1845 December (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Signed by many prominent New Yorkers of the time
- Carriage License, 1846 July 22 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  License for Joseph L. Palmer
- 5 Documents from the Department of Sewers and Drains, 1846-1847 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  Includes paylist of workmen; bills for survey from Broadway to Hudson River and for sewer repairs
- Property map of lots on Rivington & Forsythe Streets belonging to Maria A. Kissam, 1847 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  The property was leased to Mr. Quackenbos and Mr. Lawrence. The property map is on the back of a flyer for the Third Ward Whig Head Quarters
- Chronicles of the Battle of Wall Street, 1848 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Extract from a Two Years Journal in New York, 1848 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Notes on Meetings of the 16th Ward Democratic Republican Caucus, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Abstract of title of John McIntosh to a plot of ground in 16th Street purchased from William Cozzens, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Letter to William MacReady from his admirers and Letter to Nathan Darling, Esq. from the Committee to bring back the remains of General North and Colonel Duncan, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  MacReady's admirers concerned that MacReady would not continue his performance after the Astor Place Riots; General North's remains were buried in San Antonio and Colonel Duncan's remains were buried in Mobile, Alabama. Committee to return them to New York City
- Property Title Searches for Goodman & Jesup, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Searches on Property in 16th Street east of 8th Avenue
- Minutes of Meetings of Democratic Republican Party, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Includes resolutions, minutes, list of members of the Democratic Republican General Committee for 1849
- Seating Plan of Mercer Street Church, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Assorted Documents, 1850-1862 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  4 Documents: Circular for the Independent Republican Wide Awakes; Report of the Committee on County Officers on the bill of the Coroner; Board of Police acknowledgement of donation; Application of J.E. Loiseau to be French teacher
- 3 Documents, 1851-1853 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  Letter to Editor of Washington Union regarding Treason of W. Brady; Recommendation of Andrew Jackson Moore to be Custom Official; Public Reception in honor of Thomas Francis Meagherl, who escaped imprisonment in Ireland
- Assorted Documents (4 items), 1851-1857 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  Certificate for Sarah Webster for regular attendance; Permission for J.H. Edgerley to wear badge no. 37; Summons to Stephen Sedgwick to appear and pay $70.00 judgment; Complaint of Gershom Lockwood and John Dubois against Stephen Sedgwick for payment of $70.00
- Robert B. Roosevelt's Narrative of Sale of Gansevoort Property, 1852 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Assessment for Drain along Leonard Street, west of Broadway, 1854 February (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Appointment of George B. Smith as Commissioner of Deeds, 1854 August 14 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Release of Quit Rent, 1854 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Carriage License, 1854 October 17 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  G.W. Littell, Gardner A. Sage, George W. Edwards, H.N. Stebbins, W.S. Corwin, licensees
- Partial Certificate with Seal of New York signed by T. Romeyn Beck, Secretary, and G.M. Lansing, Chancellor, 1855 January 11 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Notice of Meeting of the Trustees of the Women's Medical College of New York Infirmary, 1855(?) June 16 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  Purchase of building at 26th Street near East River
- 2 Documents, 1856-1857 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Recorder of Deeds – Patrick Callaghan and Wife, Gertrude, acknowledge conveyance; Democratic Aldermen recommend to James Buchanan Capt Isaiah Rynders to US Marshalship of Southern District of New York
- Circular Letter of the New-York Historical Society, 1857 January (Box 8, Folder 46)
  Appeal to benefactors to subscribe to the Society
- Public Meeting at the Merchants Exchange, 1857 March 22 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  Taxpayers opposed to tax bill provisions to increase taxes by Common Council of New York
- First telegrams on the laying of the Trans-Atlantic Cable, 1858 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Contains letters and actual telegrams
- ALS E [Kerr], University of New York Medical Department, to father, 1859 November 17 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  includes discussions of Harper's Ferry and John Brown incident; hospitals in Europe, description of New York's poor; Van Buren's election; Mayoral election
- Agreement between George C. Tompkins and the Commissioners of the Sinking Fund, 1859-1860 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Circulars and Bills of the Rose Beneficent Association, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  Rose Beneficent Association to benefit poor white children, learn farming; "People's College"
- Contract between J. Watts De Peyster and Chauncy Barnard, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  Land at 8th Avenue and 100 Street; related documents
- Papers pertaining to a Ball given by the Citizens of New York in honor of the Prince of Wales, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  At the Academy of Music on October 12, 1860
- Freight receipts of Harnden's Express and United States Express Company, 1861-1865 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- 9 Documents relating to the Department of Public Parks, 1862-1877; undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Articles of Agreement regarding sale of property on Fifth Avenue between 58th and 59th Street; Letters to and from William Martin; Resolution regarding importance of city parks
- Admission Slip to Classes at the New York Free Aademy, 1863 January 19 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- ALS Major General John Wool to Col. Charles Darling about New York Riot, 1863 August 17 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  Thank you for putting down riots in New York City
- Papers Re: Tammany Hall, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  Lists of Officers by Ward; directions for poll elections, Committee on Tammany expenses for Oct-Dec 1857
- Souvenir of a New York Fire Department Reception in honor of Joshua Abbe, 1865 September 4 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Circular Letter signed by John Kelly, Sheriff, 1866 April 23 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  Bill for services -- $1.30
- Report of The Committee of the Board of Supervisors on the Erection of the New New York City Courthouse, 1866 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  Allegations of gross mismanagement and overspending; Committee determined that there was no evidence of mismanagement
- Notices of Arrears, 1869-1870 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Letter Concerning the Hiring of Irving Hall for a Ball, 1870 August 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  7th Company, 9th Regiment would like to hire the Hall; need to select a night.
- 3 Documents, Among them: The Petition of the Officers and Members of the First Division NGSNY, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  This folder contains 3 unrelated documents. Subscribers to the Valentine's History of New York; A letter to E.E. Miles from Alice Fletcher, Secretary of the Association for the Advancement of Women, requesting her presence at a meeting; Petition to New York State to provide a parade ground above central park for the Officers and Members of the First Division N.G.S.N.Y.
- 2 Documents, 1874-1875 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Petition to Opposing Rescinding of Resolution to print the ancient records of the city (feared it was "scheme to plunder the City Treasury"); Notice of meeting of the Woman's Medical College regarding the purchase of a college building on 26th Street.
- List of Leases, etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Draft of an Act to prevent Injury to Animals, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  People may not throw down salt, saltpeter, or other substance on any street, etc. open to the passage of animals for the purpose of dissolving snow.
- Group Letter re Remedy for abuses and dangers of patronage in the Civil Service, 1881 September 16 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  In response to the recent murderous act on the President, this group ( including Peter Cooper, William Henry Hulbert, Howard Potter, Francis Wayland, Charles Marshall, James Freeman Clarke) suggested reforms to the appointments to Civil Service
- 4 Documents, 1882-1897 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Bearer may pass; Notice of Eligibility for Letter Carrier; Appointment of Poll Watchers; Sale of Old Post Office in New York City
- Application to Play in Central Park, 1885 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Mr. F.B. Allen's school on 5th Avenue requested permission for students to play in Central Park; includes a bearer card allowing play
- Numerous Letters and Documents Concerning Tax Problems, 1885-1895 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Minutes of the Meeting to Place the Republican Party in Opposition to the Liquor Traffic, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Names of Heirs who have not signed the power, etc. In Re: The Waldron Claim, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  The Waldron Claim involved much property in Harlem (The Harlem Commons) claimed by heirs against the city, which was building the Harlem canal. Newspaper clippings regarding the case also in the folder.
- Various Licenses, Passes, etc, 1890-1913 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  Licenses for Special coaches, acknowledgements of correct transcripts; parade permit; allowing bearer to cross police lines
- Petition to the Board of Aldermen, 1894 August (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Opposition to the Metropolitan Street Railway by Property owners of St. Nicholas Avenue
- Exemption Certificate of the Fire Department of the City of New York, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Notices of Arrears, 1899-1901 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Block No. 2527; Block No. 3030
- Fragment of Letter from C.N. Taylor, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Taylor would like estimate from Mr. Baneke of value of house and grounds on Golden Mills (?) and lots at White Hall
- 3 Documents, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Rules & Regulations of Chamber; Undated inventory; history of families and houses of lower Manhattan
- Reports of William Gracie RE: Establishment of an Athenaeum, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Petition of George Stanton and Evan Bancher, Jr. to be appointed appraisers, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Report of the Committee appointed to visit Columbia College, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  John Rodgers was Chairman of Committee; Committee in general was pleased with the college.
- Petition of the Homeopathic physicians to the Common Council for a building to treat patients with Asiatic cholera, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Remarks on the Mode of Extinguishing Fires in the City of New York, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
- 16 lots on Crown Point Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Memorial adopted by Board of Directors of the New York and Harlem Railroad Company, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  Memorial to Robert Schell
- Subway Invitation and ticket for opening of New York subway, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Includes a complete invitation, a souvenir ticket and holder and a memorial from the Municipal Art Society regarding subway advertising
- Resolution of the Executive Committee of the New-York Historical Society, 1909 December 23 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  Thank Mrs. Malcolm Stuart, Mrs. J. Ferris Simmons, and Mr. Clarence Storm
- Dorothy Menkin's Reminiscences of Fox Street, The Bronx, c.1909 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Photocopy of original; Ms. Menkin wrote this piece as a senior looking back to her childhood circa 1909
- Inventory of the contents of a Bronze Chest deposited in custody of the New-York Historical Society, to be opened May 23, 1974, by the Businessmen of Lower Wall Street, 1914(?) (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Thank you Letters regarding sending new NYC Flags to schools by NYHS, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 21)